[
    {
        "question": "What happened to Harry Potter at the sorting ceremony?",
        "answer": "",
        "type": "summary",
        "id": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "List the names of the Weasley children",
        "answer": "",
        "type": "list",
        "id": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "What broom does Harry Potter own?",
        "answer": "Nimbus 2000",
        "type": "specific info",
        "id": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "List the ingreedients needed for first year students at Hogwarts",
        "answer": "",
        "type": "list",
        "id": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "What happened at the midnight duel?",
        "answer": "",
        "type": "summary",
        "id": 5
    },
    {
        "question": "What is a bezoar?",
        "answer": "",
        "type": "specific info",
        "id": 6
    },
    {
        "question": "How does Harry catch his first snitch?",
        "answer": "With his mouth",
        "type": "specific info",
        "id": 7
    },
    {
        "question": "What other house did Harry Potter almost get sorted into? ",
        "answer": "Slytherin",
        "type": "specific info",
        "id": 8
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Harry's position on the Quidditch team? ",
        "answer": "Seeker",
        "type": "specific info",
        "id": 9
    },
    {
        "question": "How many staircases does Hogwarts have?",
        "answer": "142",
        "type": "specific info",
        "id": 10
    },
    {
        "question": "Who tells Harry he's a wizard? ",
        "answer": "Hagrid",
        "type": "specific info",
        "id": 11
    },
    {
        "question": "Where in Kings Cross Station does the Hogwarts Express stop?",
        "answer": "Platform nine and three quarters",
        "type": "specific info",
        "id": 12
    },
    {
        "question": "Where are the Slytherin common rooms located?",
        "answer": "The dungeons",
        "type": "specific info",
        "id": 13
    },
    {
        "question": "How many presents did Dudley get on his 11th Birthday?",
        "answer": "36",
        "type": "specific info",
        "id": 14
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Harry's wand made of?",
        "answer": "Holly and phoenix feather",
        "type": "specific info",
        "id": 15
    },
    {
        "question": "Name the six subjects every Hogwarts student is required to study during their first two years of school",
        "answer": "Herbology, Transfiguration, Defense against the dark arts, Potions, Charms, History of Magic",
        "type": "list",
        "id": 16
    },
    {
        "question": "Who anonymously sends Harry his father's Invisibility Cloak on Christmas?",
        "answer": "Albus Dumbledore",
        "type": "specific info",
        "id": 17
    },
    {
        "question": "Name the four Hogwarts Houses.",
        "answer": "Gryffindor, HufflePuff, RavenClaw, Slytherin",
        "type": "list",
        "id": 18
    }
]
